Kiley, Dan (Dan Urban), 1912-2004. Papers of Dan Kiley: An Inventory.
Kiley, Dan (Dan Urban), 1912-2004. Papers of Dan Kiley: An Inventory.
- Landscape Architecture Drawings, / Date(s): ca. 1941 - ca. 1995; 0000; / Quantity: ca. 483 tubes; 128 folders; 2 boxes / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
  - Kensico Dam Plaza, / Date(s): 1932 - 1990; Tube: 01004; / Quantity: 39 / Dimensions: <121x121cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Plans for this public park area in Westchester County; the Dam was constructed in 1913-1917. and it, with the reservoir were acquired in 1963 as public parkland.
  - Kentucky Courts, Justice & Law Complex, / Date(s): 1978; Tube: 01005; / Quantity: 14 / Dimensions: <140x80cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Prints, in a variety of media and with a variety of annotations.
  - Doug Miller, / Date(s): 1978; Tube: 01006; / Quantity: 14 / Dimensions: <94x98cm / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Miscellaneous plans, in various media.
  - Nuclear Use Systems / Corporate Headquarters, / Date(s): 1978 - 1979; Tube: 01007; / Quantity: 6 / Dimensions: <127x92cm. / Medium: Ink; blueline prints / Support: Paper; vellum
    Note: Drawings in a variety of media and support.
    Note: A related or predecessor or agency of the Nuclear Regulatory Commission?
  - Overlake Condominiums, / Date(s): 1978; Tube: 01008; / Quantity: 7 / Dimensions: <91x61cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Various prints and film positives.
  - Winooski C.B.D., / Date(s): 1978; Tube: 01010; / Quantity: 22 / Dimensions: <97x74cm. / Medium: Pencil; ink; diazotype / Support: Vellum
    Note: Plans in a variety of media.
  - Winooski / Chace Mill Dam, / Date(s): 1978; Tube: 01011; / Quantity: 28 / Dimensions: <108x84cm. / Medium: Ink; pencil; blueline / Support: Tracing paper; vellum
    Note: Miscellaneous preliminary studies.
  - Trapp Family Lodge, / Date(s): 1979; Tube: 01014; / Quantity: 38 / Dimensions: <107x76cm. / Medium: Blueline prints / Support: Vellum
    Note: Annotated prints of the plan for the Trapp Family Lodge resort complex.
    Note: The Trapp Family, best-known as the protagonists of the musical and film The Sound of Music, turned to the "hospitality industry" as the family dispersed and their musical career waned.
  - Winooski/West Allen Street, / Date(s): 1979; Tube: 01015; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 93x68cm. / Medium: Blueline print / Support: Paper
    Note: Plan lacks legend or other identifying references.
  - Franconia Notch / I-93, / Date(s): 1979; Tube: 01016; / Quantity: 11 / Dimensions: <184x108cm. / Medium: Blackline prints / Support: Paper
    Note: Plans of existing conditions and proposed plantings at road sections.
  - Dallas Museum of Art, / Date(s): 1979; Tube: 01017; / Quantity: 79 / Dimensions: <190x106 cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary drawings, including both architect's and landscape architect's drawings; with photographs of architect's model.
    Note: The Dallas Museum was designed by Edward Larrabee Barnes.
    Published in: Cf. COMPLETE WORKS ..., pp. 94-97.
  - London Standard Chartered Bank, / Date(s): 1979; Tube: 01018; / Quantity: 113 / Dimensions: <130x97cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Architects' and landscape architect's drawings, including original drawings and annotated prints.
    Note: Designed by the architectural firm Fitzroy Robinson, the bank's 9-storey atrium was a ODK design.
    Published in: Cf. COMPLETE WORKS ... pp. 88-91.
  - Wheaton College Library, / Date(s): 1979; Tube: 01022; / Quantity: 11 / Dimensions: 3'x4' / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixedia
    Note: Site, landscape and detail drawings for landscape design related to the Wheaton College Library. an
  - Arrowhead at Vail, / Date(s): 1980; Tube: 01024; / Quantity: 4 / Dimensions: <150x95cm. / Medium: Diazotype / Support: Paper
    Note: Black-,blue-and sepia prints related to this large-scale resort planning commission.
  - East Shore Park / Phase II, / Date(s): 1980; Tube: 01025; / Quantity: 15 / Dimensions: <92x76cm. / Medium: Prints / Support: Polyester film
    Note: Includes grading plans.
    Location of associated materials: See also: Item #681 - New Haven Parks/East Shore and Item #721 - New Haven Parks/Fort Hale and East Shore.
  - Hamilton Residence, / Date(s): 1980; Tube: 01027; / Quantity: 16 / Dimensions: <107x64cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Working drawings, in mixed media.
  - Scarborough House, / Date(s): 1980 - 1981; Tube: 01028; / Quantity: 8 / Dimensions: <129x67cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Designed by the English architect William Jay for Savannah shipowner and merchant William Scarbrough in 1817, the house was subhjected to a variety of uses., at one point serving as the first public school for Afro-American children in Savannah.
    Note: Acquired, in a state of great deterioration, by the Historic Savannah Foundation in 1972, the house has undergone a series of restorations. The most recent restoration was completed in 1997, under the aegis of its current owner the Ships of the Sea Maritime Museum.
    Note: Annotated prints and drawings in a variety of media.
  - Mint Museum of Craft + Design, / Date(s): 1980; Tube: 01029; / Quantity: 16 / Dimensions: 93x62cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Annotated prints as well as preliminary drawings, annotated.
  - Detroit Institute of Arts / Sculpture Court, / Date(s): 1980; Tube: 01032; / Quantity: 4 / Dimensions: <50x39cm. / Medium: Xerographic prints / Support: Paper
    Note: Preliminary plans and sections.
    Location of associated materials: See also Item #1033 - Detroit Institute of Arts / Grounds Renovation".
  - Detroit Institute of Arts / Grounds Renovation, / Date(s): 1980; Tube: 01033; / Quantity: 16 / Dimensions: <50x39cm. / Medium: Xerographic prints / Support: Paper
    Note: Prints of Working Drawings, #1-11, together with planting plan (Sheet A9) and stats of original elevation drawings of 1924.
    Published in: Cf. THE COMPLETE WORKS ..., p. 214.
  - South Mapleton Building Upfit, / Date(s): 1980; Tube: 01037; / Quantity: 2 / Dimensions: 106x76cm. / Medium: Ink / Support: Vellum
    Note: Site plans indicate plantings and layout of landscaping for parking lot and grounds of this Cummins facility.
  - Julia Field Residence, / Date(s): 1980; Tube: 01039; / Quantity: 23 / Dimensions: <130x78cm / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Location of associated materials: See also Item #1231 - "Julia Field--1989."
  - Maynard Residence, / Date(s): 1980; Tube: 01040; / Quantity: 20 / Dimensions: <96x74cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Original drawings and annotated prints.
  - Sedgewick: Gardiner's Corner/ Office & Plaza, / Date(s): 1981; Tube: 01042; / Quantity: 19 / Dimensions: <130x93cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Annotated, re-worked drawings on prints, film and trace.
  - Bucksbaum Residence, / Date(s): 1981; Tube: 01046; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 53x41cm. / Medium: Pencil / Support: Tracing vellum
  - Bruce Smith Residence, / Date(s): 1981; Tube: 01047; / Quantity: 13 / Dimensions: <107x90cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary drawings, in pencil and marker, on tracing vellum.
  - Duncan Symes Residence, / Date(s): 1981; Tube: 01048; / Quantity: 2 / Dimensions: 109x61cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawing and print, annotated in pencil and pen.
  - San Antonio Museum of Art, / Date(s): 1981; Tube: 01049; / Quantity: 9 / Dimensions: <104x79cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Blueline prints and drawings on trace; annotated in pencil and pen.
  - David Hamilton Residence, / Date(s): 1946 - 1947; Folder: 0105; / Quantity: 4 / Dimensions: <107x56cm. / Medium: Pencil / Support: Tracing paper
    Note: Plans and details, drawn by DK; drawings (Sheet #1 lacking) dated 1947.
  - Shelburne Museum, / Date(s): 1979 - 1984; Tube: 01053; / Quantity: 46 / Dimensions: <110x91cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Annotated prints and original drawings, in a variety of media, with some correspondence.
  - K & B Plaza, / Date(s): 1981; Tube: 01054; / Quantity: 13 / Dimensions: <142x95cm / Medium: Mixed / Support: Paper
    Note: Preliminary drawings in mixed media on trace; prints of architects' drawings.
    Note: Office building originally built for John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Co., by SOM, 1960.
  - Cummins Engine Company / Madison Components Plant, / Date(s): 1981; Tube: 01055; / Quantity: 3 / Dimensions: <242x92cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Annotated prints and preliminary drawings in a variety of media.
  - Crutched Friars, / Date(s): 1982; Tube: 01057; / Quantity: 17 / Dimensions: <108x74cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Includes architects' plans and sections.
  - Mud Island North, / Date(s): 1982; Tube: 01060; / Quantity: 3 / Dimensions: <102x94cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Plans and sections in mixed media.
  - William Gregory Residence / New Site, / Date(s): 1982; Tube: 01061; / Quantity: 18 / Dimensions: <137x107cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Site and planting plans in mixed media.
    Note: Identified as "new site" for this former Kiley client.
    Published in: Cf. COMPLETE WORKS ..., pp. 70-73 for an account of the "original" Gregory property designed by Kiley.
  - Fountain Place, / Date(s): 1982; Tube: 01062; / Quantity: 40 / Dimensions: <125x92cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary and working drawings on film, together with sepia prints.
    Note: Cf. also, Fountain Place, [videorecording] ... Aaron Kiley, photographer. (VisRes SB470 .K55 F67x)
    Published in: "Kiley Revisited", Landscape Architecture, August 1988, 8, pp. 58-89; "The People Commandeer a Plaza", Landscape Architecture,. January 1991, 1, pp. 44-46; "Two Dallas Towers", Texas Architect,.
    Published in: July/August 1987, 4, pp. 4-2-45; "The Dallas Waterworks", Cite, The Architecture and Design Review of Houston, Fall 1992/Spring 1993, 29, pp.31-32.
    Published in: "Dallas Oasis", Architectural Review,August 1988, 184, pp. 7-71; "Allied Bank Tower at Fountain Place", Places, 1987, 4:4, pp. 34-35.
    Published in: "Urban Public Spaces", Center: A Journal ..., 1985, 1, pp. 84-93.
    Published in: Cf. COMPLETE WORKS ..., pp. 98-105.
  - Medical Center Hospital, / Date(s): 1982; Tube: 01065; / Quantity: 2 / Dimensions: 107x92cm. / Medium: Ink / Support: Polyester film
  - Topnotch at Stowe, / Date(s): 1983; Tube: 01071; / Quantity: 10 / Dimensions: <149x103cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings and annotated printes in mixed media.
  - Trinity University / Stieren Sculpture, / Date(s): 1983; Tube: 01072; / Quantity: 5 / Dimensions: 61x43cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes pencil drawings and annotated prints.
  - Colorado Rocky Mountain School, / Date(s): 1983; Tube: 01073; / Quantity: 4 / Dimensions: 94x62cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Miscellaneous prints.
  - National Sculpture Garden, / Date(s): 1983; Tube: 01074; / Quantity: 83 / Dimensions: <210x107cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Original drawings and annotated prints, in a variety of media.
    Note: One of a series of ODK office files related to the National Gallery complex.
    Location of associated materials: See also: Item #1106 and Item #1217 for related materials.
    Published in: Cf. COMPLETE WORKS ..., pp. 80-83.
  - Cummins Engine Company / Indianapolis, / Date(s): 1983; Tube: 01077; / Quantity: 14 / Dimensions: <124x90cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings found with iitem #1001, Cummins Main Plant, Forecourt buildings 14 and 73 studies.
  - Candlestick Point Park, / Date(s): 1983; Tube: 01079; / Quantity: 29 / Dimensions: <118x83cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: A melange of drawings, in mixed media, ranging from preliminaries to working drawings.
  - Vasiliou Residence, / Date(s): 1982; Tube: 01080; / Quantity: 2 / Dimensions: 92x61cm. / Medium: Blueline prints / Support: Paper
    Note: Prints annotated in marker.
  - Middlebury College / Master Plan, / Date(s): 1984; Tube: 01083; / Quantity: 2 / Dimensions: 107x76cm. / Medium: Blueline prints / Support: Paper
  - Christian Theological Seminary / Housing, / Date(s): 1983; Tube: 01085; / Quantity: 3 / Dimensions: <106x80cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: A wide range of drawings, together with bound set of architect's working drawings.
    Location of associated materials: See also Item #523.
  - Reynolds Residence, / Date(s): 1985 - 1986; Tube: 01086; / Quantity: 62 / Dimensions: <76x121cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings related to Reynolds Residence.
  - State University of New York at Purchase, / Date(s): 1968 - 1984; Tube: 01089; / Quantity: 14 / Dimensions: <93x117cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Annotated baseline prints; site related to Barnes' Performing Arts Center.
  - Dulles Airport / CIT, / Date(s): 1984; Tube: 01091; / Quantity: 34 / Dimensions: <115x77cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
  - Heritage Landing, / Date(s): 1984; Tube: 01092; / Quantity: 21 / Dimensions: <120x78cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes blueline and sepias prints, architects' drawings and preliminary drawings from ODK.
  - Silicon Valley Financial Center, / Date(s): 1984; Tube: 01093; / Quantity: 7 / Dimensions: <107x94cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Original drawings and prints.
  - NCNB National Bank, / Date(s): 1984; Tube: 01095; / Quantity: 276 / Dimensions: <107x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: A substantial file, including both original drawings as well as prints, for this well-known Kiley commission, completed in 1988.
    Note: Cf. also Tampa Bank [videorecording] ... Aaron Kiley, photographer. (VisRes SB470.K55 T35)
    Published in: "The 1991 Awards for Excellence in Architecture", Florida Architect, November/December 1991, 38, pp. [7]-15.
    Published in: "North Carolina National Bank Plaza", Landscape Architecture, December 1988, 78, pp. 88-91.
    Published in: "Completato l'edificio per la NCBN ...", Casabella, March 1990, vol. 54, no. 566, p. 33.
    Published in: Cf. COMPLETE WORKS ..., pp. 106-111.
  - Vanderbilt University, / Date(s): 1985; Tube: 01100; / Quantity: 68 / Dimensions: <156x109cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings, annotated prints and photographs.
  - Criswell Residence, / Date(s): 1985; Tube: 01104; / Quantity: 138 / Dimensions: <108x96cm / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Prints and drawings (including preliminaries in the hand of DK).
    Note: Includes blueline prints of street, sewer and drainage plans.
    Biographical note: Criswell was the original developer of Fountain Place.
    Published in: Cf. COMPLETE WORKS ..., p.215.
  - National Sculpture Garden, / Date(s): 1985; Tube: 01106; / Quantity: 44 / Dimensions: <127x92cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Original drawings and annotated prints in a variety of media.
    Location of associated materials: See also Items #1074 and #1217.
  - St. John's Seminary /Abbey, / Date(s): 1985; Tube: 01109; / Quantity: 65 / Dimensions: <192x97cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: There are variant references in title blocks and notes to "St. John's Abbey", "St. John's College", etc. This file appears to be conflated with ODK Project List #1149.
  - Faith Trust, / Date(s): 1985; Tube: 01110; / Quantity: 50 / Dimensions: <175x99cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary and design development drawings in mixed media; file includes plans of existing landscape.
  - United States Embassy / Amman, / Date(s): 1985; Tube: 01112; / Quantity: 34 / Dimensions: <141x79cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary competition drawings, in mixed media.
    Published in: "Ambivalent Symbol: United States Embassy ...", Architectural Record, May 1993, vol. 181, n.5, pp. [66]-73.
  - Joslyn Art Museum, / Date(s): 1985; Tube: 01113; / Quantity: 18 / Dimensions: <87x85cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes preliminary drawings in mixed media, bound set of architect's drawings, USGS maps and other background material.
  - Lakeshore Park, / Date(s): 1985; Tube: 01119; / Quantity: 38 / Dimensions: <120x82cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Subtitled: "Proposal for a Park Connecting the Chicago Water Tower to Lake Michigan."
  - Bryan Residence, / Date(s): 1982 - 1986; Tube: 01120; / Quantity: 58 / Dimensions: <150x92cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: ODK drawings dated 1986; file include's architect's working drawings dated 1982.
    Published in: Hugh Newell Jacobsen... Washington, AIA Press, 1988, pp. 268-277.
    Published in: "Architecture: Hugh Newell Jacobsen", Architectural Digest, July 1988, 7, pp. 148-188.
    Published in: Cf. COMPLETE WORKS ..., pp. 214-215.
  - Heath Residence, / Date(s): 1988; Tube: 01121; / Quantity: 15 / Dimensions: <48"x36" / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Plans for additional work on the Heath residence's grounds; Kiley son-in-law Chris Dunn had worked on the site previously.
  - Steven Jobs Residence, / Date(s): 1986; Tube: 01126; / Quantity: 17 / Dimensions: <112x95cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes drawings in a variety of media, prints and surveys.
    Note: The property subsequently became a source of controversy as the Town of Woodside illegally approved Jobs' request for its demolition in 2007.
    Note: The town's decision was subsequently overruled by a California court.
    Note: The Jacklingf House was designed in the 1920s by George Washington Smith for copper magnate Daniel Jackling, in Smith's signature "Spanish Colonial" style.
  - Elliott Residence, / Date(s): 1986; Tube: 01127; / Quantity: 46 / Dimensions: <108x74cm / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Landscaping plans related to Elliott Residence.
  - Lewis Residence, / Date(s): 1986; Tube: 01128; / Quantity: 46 / Dimensions: <107x76cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Landscaping plans related to Lewis Residence.
  - Lewis Farm, / Date(s): 1986; Tube: 01129; / Quantity: 14 / Dimensions: <107x91cm / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes drawings and annotated prints, in mixed media.
  - Minnesota State Capitol Competition, / Date(s): 1986; Tube: 01130; / Quantity: 15 / Dimensions: <180x93cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes ODK preliminary drawings as well as prints of competition materials.
  - Shapiro Residence, / Date(s): 1985; Tube: 01133; / Quantity: 9 / Dimensions: <92x61cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings and prints in a variety of media; job listed as "1994" in ODK listing and publications.
    Published in: "Prairie Home Companions", House and Garden, November 1996, pp. 196-203.
    Published in: Cf. COMPLETE WORKS ..., pp. 150-153.
  - Carnegie Center, / Date(s): 1986; Tube: 01143; / Quantity: 137 / Dimensions: <122x87cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Includes drawings for signage and lighting.
  - Lewis/Hobart House, / Date(s): 1986; Tube: 01144; / Quantity: 56 / Dimensions: <89x62cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Some variants in reference to project: OKS: "Lewis-Hobart"; architect: "Lewis."
  - Bostwick Property, / Date(s): 1986; Tube: 01145; / Quantity: 8 / Dimensions: <148x86cm. / Medium: Diazotypes / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes annotated prints and aerial photograph.
  - IBM / Purchase, / Date(s): 1986; Tube: 01147; / Quantity: 4 / Dimensions: <91x60cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Material in a variety of formats.
  - Tolman Property, / Date(s): 1986; Tube: 01150; / Quantity: 17 / Dimensions: <159x92cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Job unrecorded in conventional sources.
  - Greensboro Cultural Center, / Date(s): 1987; Tube: 01152; / Quantity: 111 / Dimensions: <109x76cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Original drawings and prints, in a variety of media, for the grounds of the Greensboro Cultural Center.
    Note: The Center is composed of a group of existing structures which housed the Greensboro Daily News.
    Published in: Architectural Record, March 1991, 79, pp. 152-153.
  - United States Judiciary Building Quadrangle, / Date(s): 1987; Tube: 01153; / Quantity: 15 / Dimensions: <44x36cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes annotated architectural drawings and tree surveys.
    Published in: "Seven Schemes Proposed ...", Architecture, Aug. 1989, v. 78, no. 8, pp. 17-18.
    Published in: "Completing D.C.'s Federal Triangle", Progressive Architecture, Oct. 1987, vol. 68, no. 10, pp. 25-26.
  - Vila-Barret Residence, / Date(s): 1987; Tube: 01154; / Quantity: 36 / Dimensions: <147x107cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Survey notes location: "Boston (West Roxbury) Mass." Associated architect's vita sites in Jamaica Plain and notes house was unbuilt.
  - Gulfstream-Jacaranda Park, / Date(s): 1987; Tube: 01155; / Quantity: 16 / Dimensions: <110x78cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary drawings in mixed media, with bound set of architect's drawings.
  - Pelham Green, / Date(s): 1987; Tube: 01156; / Quantity: 30 / Dimensions: <122x97cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Ink and pencil drawings and annotations on prints, film and trace.
  - Hall Residence, / Date(s): 1987 - 1991; Tube: 01157; / Quantity: 268 / Dimensions: <72x198cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: An extensive file of drawings related to the grounds of the Hall house. Client D.J. Hall, CEO of Hallmark.
    Published in: Dan Kiley: The Complete Works ...1999, pp. 118-123.
  - Gateway Center, / Date(s): 1987; Tube: 01158; / Quantity: 12 / Dimensions: 107x76cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings from the ODK and the architects' firm.
    Published in: North Carolina Architecture, July-Aug., 1987, pp. 7-9.
  - Henry Moore Sculpture Garden, / Date(s): 1987; Tube: 01159; / Quantity: 186 / Dimensions: <91x183cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary, presentation and working drawings in a wide range of media.
    Published in: Dan Kiley: The Complete Works ... 1999, pp. 112-117.
    Published in: "In This Sculpture Garden", Museum News, September/October 1989, 68:5, pp. 19-21.
    Published in: "The Nelson-Atkins Henry Moore Sculpture Garden", Inland Architect, July/August 1989, 33:4, p. 13, p.16.dt
    Published in: "A Dozen Moores in Kansas City", Progressive Architecture, September 1989, 70:9, p. 23.
    Published in: "Henry Moore in America's Heartland", Landscape Architecture, April 1989, 79:3, pp. 78-81.
  - Pemberton Square, / Date(s): 1987; Tube: 01160; / Quantity: 13 / Dimensions: <102x71cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary drawings and annotated architects' drawings.
  - Alexander Residence, / Date(s): 1987; Tube: 01161; / Quantity: 13 / Dimensions: <91x75cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes architect's working drawings as well as preliminary drawings by the ODK.
  - Hilllberry/Kandrian Residence, / Date(s): 1987; Tube: 01162; / Quantity: 25 / Dimensions: <107x76cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes preliminary drawings, planting plans and blueline prints of architect's drawings.
  - James Hunter Residence, / Date(s): 1987; Tube: 01163; / Quantity: 14 / Dimensions: <107x76cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary drawings, together with miscellaneous plans.
  - Brickell Avenue, / Date(s): 1987 - 1988; Tube: 01164; / Quantity: 59 / Dimensions: <161x92cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes related plans of area structures and landscaping.
    Published in: Cf. COMPLETE WORKS ... p. 215.